Viewers all over the world,
the bible says, Come unto me that all ye that labour,
come, all ye that are troubled, and I will give you rest.
I say in the name of Jesus, receive rest from all of your troubles.
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua,
touch the screen by faith in Jesus name.
Because of Christ began to receive rest!
Begin to receive rest from all of your troubles.
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua,
touch the screen by faith in Jesus name.
You that are sick be healed in the name of Jesus!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua,
touch the screen by faith in Jesus name.
You that are troubled,
you that are suffering,
receive rest in the name Jesus!
Rest from all of your troubles, in the name of Jesus.
I can hear someone say, "I am free!"
In the name of Jesus!
Thank you!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest: prophecies, deliverances, service and testimonies,
from the Synagogue Church Of All Nations
Emmanuel TV. Changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.